<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</description>
    <image>
      <title>Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/images/yatan-logomjsmtr.webp</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/images/yatan-logomjsmtr.webp</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:11:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An old story about a Chinese Farmer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chinesefarmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:38:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chinesefarmer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;chinese-farmer-story&#34;&gt;Chinese Farmer Story&lt;/h1&gt;


    
    &lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/byQrdnq7_H0?autoplay=1&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=1&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;
      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin (Self) Assisted Therapy Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/psilocybin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:38:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/psilocybin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview-of-how-assisted-therapy-works&#34;&gt;Overview of how assisted therapy works&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pre-treatment preparation: Patients undergo an extensive screening process to determine their eligibility for psilocybin-assisted therapy. They receive preparatory sessions to educate them about the treatment, manage expectations, and establish rapport with the therapist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psilocybin administration: During the psilocybin session, patients are given a single dose of psilocybin in a controlled, supportive environment with trained therapists present. The dose is typically administered orally, either in capsules or mixed with a liquid. The patient is then instructed to lie down, wear eyeshades, and listen to music.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ode to the Mountain and the Bench</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/an-ode-to-the-mountain-and-the-bench/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/an-ode-to-the-mountain-and-the-bench/</guid>
      <description>Guide to emoji usage in Hugo and DoIt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lista de Compras Keto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ketolista/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ketolista/</guid>
      <description>Lista de compras Keto Flex</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make a Decision</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/decision/</guid>
      <description>How to Make a Decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alzheimer Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/alzheimers-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/alzheimers-resources/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately my family has had a history of Alzheimer and dementia, my two grandmothers died of it and now it has affected my mother as well.
So I want to share a few resources to learn about Alzheimer and also to give some hope to those who are family or are care partners (formerly caregivers)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally follow Dr. Bredesen&amp;rsquo;s logic of ReCODE protocol (Reversing Cognitive Decline) and all conventional neurologists say it can&amp;rsquo;t harm, whilst functional neurologists say its the only way forward.
Studies are still small but promising.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 steps to being a great guest (with any kind of host)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/greatguest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:48:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/greatguest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After many years of moving or traveling a lot and being content with a laptop, a candle and a place to sleep, I got a place where I could host people. And through that experience of hosting a lot of people, friends, friends of friends, parents, and more, I realized that my view on being a good guest was maybe not everybody&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time a new friend stayed with me for a few weeks. I had met her not too long ago on an island and she was coming to Berlin so I offered to host her. At the time my dad just happened to be staying with me in the guestroom, so we were sharing the space. My friend is a lovely person but after a week of friction my dad asked me &amp;ldquo;Are you in love with her, are you sleeping with her?&amp;rdquo; and when my answer was no, he looked at me baffled &amp;ldquo;why are you tolerating her behaviour, cant she go somewhere else?&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conscious Leadership Clearing Call</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clearing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To engage in a clearing conversation that allows us speak plainly to each other and understand each other’s stories, feelings and desires
If we have time / get to a point that we are ready to move on, we can move to actionable next steps on how to work better together going forward&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please share with the other person in advance, an email or document with 1 (max 2) situations following the clearing framework (see below).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yatan Blumenthal - Curriculum Vitae EN</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cven/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cven/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Berlin / Bogota ● +4915739625098 ● &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yatan.co&#34;&gt;www.yatan.co&lt;/a&gt; ● &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:me@yatan.co&#34;&gt;me@yatan.co&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yatan Blumenthal is an international professional with 10+ years experience in project management, sales, team building, community building, technology building, research and training and coaching.
Trained as mindfulness &amp;amp; emotional intelligence teacher for work he always enjoys building great teams with a great culture. Also trained as a full stack web developer, he is very comfortable in working in tech focused teams. He has worked with corporates, startups and NGOs and International organisations in Asia, Latin America and Europe. He thrives in challenging  environments with steep learning curves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yatan Blumenthal - Hoja De Vida</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cves/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:me@yatan.co&#34;&gt;me@yatan.co&lt;/a&gt; ● +4915739625098 ● &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yatan.co&#34;&gt;www.yatan.co&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;resumen&#34;&gt;Resumen&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yatan Blumenthal Vargas es un profesional con experiencia en management, manejo de projectos, coaching, technology building y emprendimiento creativo. Es certificado como un entrenador de inteligencia emocional Search Inside Yourself y tambien desarrollador de software. Ha trabajado armando programas de educacion y manejando proyectos con corporates, startups y ONGs en Asia, America Latina y Europa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;educación&#34;&gt;Educación&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;profesional&#34;&gt;Profesional&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;05/2018-05/2019 |&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Search Inside Yourself Certified Teacher&lt;/strong&gt;; Entrenador en mindfulness z Inteligencia Emocional con enfoque en liderazgo y excelencia de trabajo de equipos.
**
&lt;strong&gt;04/2018-07/2018 |&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Full Stack Web Developer&lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;em&gt;9-week intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES2015, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
