<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Emotional Intelligence on Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/emotional-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Emotional Intelligence on Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</description>
    <image>
      <title>Yatan Blumenthal Vargas</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/images/yatan-logomjsmtr.webp</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/images/yatan-logomjsmtr.webp</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/emotional-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Resilience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/emotional-intelligence/adaptive-resilience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/emotional-intelligence/adaptive-resilience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Practical tools to work more skillfully with difficult emotions, uncertainty and change, leading to increased team performance and well-being
Bring Adaptive Resilience to your organization&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adaptive resilience is the ability to recover from adversity, adapt and thrive. It builds the capacity to be productive, resourceful, and creative while dealing with changing circumstances or adversity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This interactive program uses a mindfulness-based approach to build the behaviors, mental habits, and practices that promote personal resilience while growing a culture of resilience within teams and organizations. This 3-part series is available for in-person delivery or as live online training.
Program Overview&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Inside Yourself (SIY)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/search-inside-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/search-inside-yourself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-program&#34;&gt;The Program&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Search Inside Yourself - Leadership Training
Originally developed at Google, Search Inside Yourself teaches practical mindfulness, emotional intelligence and leadership tools to unlock your full potential at work and in life.
Bring Search Inside Yourself to your organization
Program Overview&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Search Inside Yourself takes an evidence-based approach combining neuroscience, attention-training and emotional intelligence. The program provides practical tools that can be applied immediately in life or at work. We start with a foundation of mindfulness, and build the core emotional intelligence domains that lead to outstanding leadership.
Mindfulness:EI:Neuroscience triad
Program Structure&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
